const taskTranslateWord = {
  title: "Перевод с анлийского на русский",
  questions: [
    {
      question: "street",
      correctAnswer: ["улица", "деловой", "улочка"]
    },
    {
      question: "company",
      correctAnswer: ["компания", "фирма", "общество", "товарищество"]
    },
    {
      question: "number",
      correctAnswer: ["номер", "количество", "число", "цифра", "сумма"]
    },
    {
      question: "world",
      correctAnswer: [
        "мир",
        "свет",
        "вселенная",
        "общество",
        "царство",
        "кругозор"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "house",
      correctAnswer: ["дом", "жилище", "театр", "здание", "палата", "гостиница"]
    },
    {
      question: "woman",
      correctAnswer: ["женщина", "баба", "служанка", "любовница", "уборщица"]
    },
    {
      question: "people",
      correctAnswer: [
        "люди",
        "народ",
        "жители",
        "население",
        "нация",
        "служащие"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "place",
      correctAnswer: [
        "место",
        "местечко",
        "город",
        "положение",
        "площадь",
        "жилище"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "school",
      correctAnswer: [
        "школа",
        "обучение",
        "направление",
        "занятия в школе",
        "класс"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "country",
      correctAnswer: [
        "страна",
        "местность",
        "родина",
        "деревня",
        "отечество",
        "территория"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "point",
      correctAnswer: ["точка", "балл", "пункт", "момент", "очко", "дело"]
    },
    {
      question: "family",
      correctAnswer: ["семья", "семейство", "род", "содружество"]
    },
    {
      question: "power",
      correctAnswer: [
        "власть",
        "мощность",
        "сила",
        "мощь",
        "энергия",
        "способность"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "money",
      correctAnswer: [
        "деньги",
        "денежные суммы",
        "богатство",
        "монетные валюты"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "market",
      correctAnswer: ["рынок", "базар", "торговля", "спрос", "сбыт", "магазин"]
    },
    {
      question: "report",
      correctAnswer: [
        "доклад",
        "отчет",
        "сообщение",
        "рапорт",
        "репортаж",
        "донесение"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "friend",
      correctAnswer: [
        "друг",
        "подруга",
        "приятель",
        "знакомый",
        "товарищ",
        "приятельница"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "parent",
      correctAnswer: [
        "родитель",
        "предок",
        "родительница",
        "причина",
        "праотец",
        "приемный отец"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "person",
      correctAnswer: [
        "человек",
        "лицо",
        "личность",
        "особа",
        "персонаж",
        "субъект"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "reason",
      correctAnswer: [
        "причина",
        "повод",
        "основание",
        "разум",
        "рассудок",
        "довод"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "morning",
      correctAnswer: ["утро", "утренняя заря", "начало", "ранний период"]
    },
    {
      question: "figure",
      correctAnswer: [
        "рисунок",
        "цифра",
        "фигура",
        "диаграмма",
        "образ",
        "личность"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "price",
      correctAnswer: ["цена", "расценка", "ценность", "жертва"]
    },
    {
      question: "support",
      correctAnswer: [
        "поддержка",
        "помощь",
        "опора",
        "подставка",
        "суппорт",
        "кронштейн"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "health",
      correctAnswer: [
        "здоровье",
        "самочувствие",
        "здравие",
        "жизнеспособность",
        "благосостояние"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "field",
      correctAnswer: [
        "поле",
        "область",
        "месторождение",
        "пространство",
        "поприще"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "example",
      correctAnswer: ["пример", "образец", "экземпляр", "урок"]
    },
    {
      question: "action",
      correctAnswer: [
        "действие",
        "акция",
        "деятельность",
        "воздействие",
        "поступок",
        "результат",
        "эффект",
        "поведение",
        "влияние"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "paper",
      correctAnswer: ["бумага", "документ", "обои"]
    },
    {
      question: "table",
      correctAnswer: [
        "стол",
        "таблица",
        "расписание",
        "доска",
        "трапеза",
        "плита"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "animal",
      correctAnswer: ["животное", "зверь", "скотина"]
    },
    {
      question: "picture",
      correctAnswer: [
        "рисунок",
        "картина",
        "изображение",
        "картинка",
        "представление",
        "образ"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "child",
      correctAnswer: ["ребенок", "дитя", "сын", "малыш", "младенец", "потомок"]
    },
    {
      question: "horse",
      correctAnswer: [
        "лошадь",
        "конь",
        "конница",
        "кавалерия",
        "козлы",
        "рама",
        "лошадка"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "color",
      correctAnswer: ["цвет", "краска", "колорит", "оттенок", "свет", "тон"]
    },
    {
      question: "summer",
      correctAnswer: ["лето", "год", "балка"]
    },
    {
      question: "letter",
      correctAnswer: [
        "письмо",
        "буква",
        "символ",
        "послание",
        "литера",
        "шрифт"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "river",
      correctAnswer: ["река", "поток", "речка"]
    },
    {
      question: "potato",
      correctAnswer: ["картофель", "картошка", "картофелина", "дырка"]
    },
    {
      question: "mouse",
      correctAnswer: ["мышь", "мышка", "мышонок"]
    },
    {
      question: "sugar",
      correctAnswer: ["сахар", "сахарок"]
    },
    {
      question: "window",
      correctAnswer: ["окно", "окошко", "витрина"]
    }
  ]
};
export default taskTranslateWord;
